takecareof.com 2019-07-15

# Care/of: Personalized Daily Vitamin Packs

__Last Updated: August 9, 2017  
__  
We at Noho Health Inc. (“Noho Health,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) have created this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Noho Health in connection with our Services, which are made available to you through our website located at Takecareof.com (the “Website”).

##### Description of Users and Acceptance of Terms

This Privacy Policy applies to visitors to the Website, who view only publicly-available content (“Visitors”), and customers who have purchased a Subscription to our Services (“Customers”).

By visiting our Website, Visitors are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. By purchasing a Subscription, each Customer is agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. 

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use. 

##### The Information We Collect and/or Receive

In the course of operating the Website, and the Services, Noho Health will collect (and/or receive) the following types of information. You authorize us to collect and/or receive such information. 

  1. Personal Information:   
In order for us to help you build your Personalized Care/of Packs, you will be asked to provide us with personal information about yourself, such as your first name, e-mail address, gender, age and zipcode. If you would like to purchase a Subscription to our Services, you will be required to provide us with additional personal information about yourself, such as your name, and shipping address. All information that we receive under this section is collectively called “Personal Information.” We do not collect any Personal Information from Visitors when they use the Website, unless they provide such information voluntarily. 
  2. Wellness Information:   
In order for us to help you build your Personalized Care/of Packs, you will be asked to provide us with some information about your health and wellness, including but not limited to, your short-term and long-term health goals, your diet, your lifestyle, your views about health/wellness, and medical conditions that you have experienced or that exist in your family (collectively, the “Wellness Information”).
  3. Billing Information:   
In order to purchase a Subscription to our Services, you will be required to provide certain information in addition to the Personal Information noted above. Such information may include a credit card number, expiration date, billing zipcode, activation code, and similar information (collectively, the “Billing Information). Such Billing Information will be collected and processed by our Third Party Payment Vendor pursuant to the terms and conditions of their privacy policies and terms of use, and we do not obtain access to any Billing Information.
  4. Order Information:   
When Customers place an order for their Personalized Care/of Packs, we will also collect and/or receive certain information, including but not limited to, the Products in their Personalized Care/of Packs (“Order Information”).
  5. Other Information:   
In addition to the Personal Information, Wellness Information, Order Information, and the Billing Information, we may collect additional information (collectively, the “Other Information”). Such Other Information may include: 
    1. From Your Activity:   
In an ongoing effort to improve the Website and the Services, we automatically collect certain information when Visitors visit the Website, and when Customers use the Services. Such information includes, without limitation, IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website Visitors visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Services.
    2. From Cookies:   
We collect information using “cookie” technology. Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on your computer’s or mobile device’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to help us collect Other Information and to enhance your experience using the Services. If you do not want us to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your computer or mobile device. Please consult your Internet browser’s documentation for information on how to do this and how to delete persistent cookies. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from us, the Services may not function properly.
    3. Third-Party Analytics:   
We may use one or more third-party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Services, compile reports on activity, collect demographic data, analyze performance metrics, and collect and evaluate other information relating to the Services and mobile and Internet usage. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By accessing and using the Services, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. The third parties we currently work with are those listed below. These third parties may change from time to time, but in each case we will provide you with the links to view these organizations' privacy policies and find out more about what data they hold about you, what they do with it, and how to opt-out from certain data collection. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website, and the Services.

For Google Analytics, please visit: <https://www.google.com/analytics>   
For Segment.io, please visit: <https://segment.com/docs/legal/privacy/>   
For Intercom, please visit: <https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy>   
For Mixpanel, please visit: <https://mixpanel.com/privacy/>   
For Hotjar, please visit: <https://www.hotjar.com/privacy>

The Information Collected by or Through Third-Party Advertising Companies  
We may share, or we may permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies and other third party services, to collect, information about your use of our Website over time so that they may play or display ads on our Website, on other devices you may use, and on other websites, apps or services, including on Facebook. It is important to note, however, that we do not share any of your Personal Information with these parties. These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect this non-personal information for such purposes. Pixel tags enable us, and these third-party advertisers, to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site. You may opt-out of the tailoring of advertising based on information we collect. To learn more about interest-based advertising and how you may be able to opt-out of some of this advertising, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices,> and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s resources atwww.aboutads.info/choices, and you may also adjust your ad preferences through your Facebook settings. 

##### How We Use and Share Information

You authorize us to use the Personal Information, Wellness Information, Order Information and the Other Information (collectively, the “Information”) to provide and improve the Website and the Services; to solicit your feedback; and to inform you about our products and services and those of our promotional partners. 

You also authorize us to use and/or share Information as described below.

  * Agents, Providers and Related Third Parties:   
We may engage other companies and individuals to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing technical assistance, order fulfillment, customer service, and marketing assistance. These other companies will have access to the Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. We may also share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, or other companies under common control with us.
  * Aggregated Information:   
In an ongoing effort to better understand our Visitors, and Customers, we may analyze Personal Information with Other Information in anonymized and aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website and the Services and for our own research purposes. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. 
  * Business Transfers:   
As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.
  * Legal Requirements:   
We may disclose your Information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action or disclosure is necessary or appropriate to: (i) operate the Platform, (ii) comply with any legal obligation, report unlawful activity, cooperate with law enforcement, or protect against legal liability, (iii) protect and defend our rights, property, personnel, suppliers, sponsors, agents or licensors, or (iv) protect the personal safety of vendors, users of the Platform or the public. 

We know how important it is to keep the Information you’ve entrusted to us confidential. We will not rent, sell or share your Information with third parties except as specifically approved or under the circumstances described above. If you do not want us to use or disclose Information collected about you in the ways identified in this policy, you should not use the Website or Services.

##### How We Protect Your Information

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Platform may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. 

##### Accessing and Modifying Information and Communication Preferences

When registering with our Website, customers may opt out of having their Information used for purposes not directly related to the provision of goods or services through our Website. Customers may also access, remove, review, and/or make changes to the same by following the instructions found on the Website. In addition, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any Noho Health marketing e-mail. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account with Noho Health.

##### Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents

The Website, the Services, and their servers are operated in the United States. Please be aware that your information, may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to use the Website and/or the Services, you hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consent to such transfer, processing, and use in the United States and elsewhere. 

##### External Websites

The Website and the Services may contain links to External Sites. Noho Health has no control over the privacy practices or the content of these External Sites. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those External Sites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

##### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide us Personal Information without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

##### California Residents

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have an established business relationship with Noho Health may choose to opt out of our sharing their Personal Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and (1) you wish to opt out; or (2) you wish to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for the direct marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to [help@takecareof.com](mailto:help@takecareof.com) or write to us at:

Noho Health, Inc.  
9 Great Jones St., Suite 4   
New York, NY 10012 

In addition, Noho Health does not monitor, recognize, or honor any opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser “Do Not Track” settings and/or signals.

##### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on the Website. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) prior to the changes becoming effective. By accessing the Website and/or using the Services after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, our use of the Information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect the Information. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

##### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Noho Health via e-mail at [help@takecareof.com](mailto:help@takecareof.com) with “Privacy Policy” in the subject line.
